When I get home
Cuando llegue a casa
You better not be there
Será mejor que no estés ahí
We're placin' bets you won't
Estamos apostando que no
Shed your modesty
Deja tu modestia
And the only thing to leave behind
Y la única cosa que dejarás atrás
Is your own skin on the floor
Es tu propia piel en el suelo
Don't you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
No te escondas (Ah-ah-ah)
Manifest a ceiling
Formas un techo
When you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
Cuando te escondes (Ah-ah-ah)
Searchin' for that feelin'
Buscando ese sentimiento
Just like an "I love you" (Ooh, ooh)
Como un "te amo" (Ooh, ooh)
That isn't words (Ooh, ooh)
Que no son palabras (Ooh, ooh)
Like a song he wrote, that's never heard (Ah-ah-ah)
Como una canción que él escribió que nunca es escuchada (Ah-ah-ah)
Don't you sh…
No te shh...
When you get home
Cuando llegas a casa
You barely recognize the pictures
Apenas reconoces las fotos
They put in a frame
Que pusieron en los marcos
'Cause you shed your modеsty
Porque dejastе tu modestia
Don't circle the track
No des vueltas еn la pista
Take what you havе
Toma lo que tienes
And leave your skin on the floor
Y deja tu piel en el suelo
Don't you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
No te escondas (Ah-ah-ah)
Manifest a ceiling
Formas un techo
When you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
Cuando te escondes (Ah-ah-ah)
Searchin' for that feelin'
Buscando ese sentimiento
Just like an "I love you" (Ooh, ooh)
Como un "te amo" (Ooh, ooh)
That isn't words (Ooh, ooh)
Que no son palabras (Ooh, ooh)
Like a song he wrote (Ah-ah-ah)
Como una canción que él escribió (Ah-ah-ah)
That's never heard
Que nunca es escuchada
When I get home
Cuando llegue a casa
Boy, you better not be there
Chico, será mejor que no estés ahí
You're long gone
Espero ya estés lejos
Shed your modesty
Deja tu modestia
Don't circle the track
No des vueltas en la pista
Just break the cycle in half
Sólo rompe el ciclo por la mitad
And leave your skin on the floor
Y deja tu piel en el suelo
Don't you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
No te escondas (Ah-ah-ah)
Manifest a ceiling
Formas un techo
When you shy away (Ah-ah-ah)
Cuando te escondes (Ah-ah-ah)
Searchin' for that feelin'
Buscando ese sentimiento
Just like an "I love you" (Ooh, ooh)
Como un "te amo" (Ooh, ooh)
That isn't words (Ooh, ooh)
Que no son palabras (Ooh, ooh)
Like a song he wrote (Ah-ah-ah)
Como una canción que él escribió (Ah-ah-ah)
That's never heard
Que nunca es escuchada
That's never heard (Ah- ah-ah, ah-ah-ah)
(Ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah)
An "I love you"
Un "te amo"
That isn't words
Que no son palabras
Like a song he wrote
Como una canción que él escribió
That's never heard
Que nunca es escuchada
Don't you shy away
No te escondas